Rainbow Spring
うた
イナカモノ
うさ
鎖那
シト
赤飯
なゆごろう
のぶなが
向日葵
りょーくん
どうが・いらすと
おんがく
ふわりP
Vocals
Inakamono
Usa
Sana
Shito
Sekihan
Nayugorou
Nobunaga
Himawari
Ryo-kun
Video & Illust.
Music
FuwariP
A single page of stillness passing through
うさ
Usa
Extending into the distance, overlapping with wavering shadows
なゆごろう
Nayugorou
Shoeprints pushing through the sand on the opposite shore
The river's water flowing across my hand
イナカモノ
Inakamono
The worn-out letters at the bus stop
鎖那
Sana
Scraped up white lines
シト
Shito
The things I traced with a slightly bent finger
リょーくん
Ryo-kun
Those days disappear into long hair...
向日葵
Himawari
The things we saw, the things we found
赤飯
Sekihan
gently play the sky, returning to us
Streaming light leads us
のぶなが
Nobunaga
CONGRATULATIONS ON GRADUATION
Congrats!
to the next day sleeping in the distance
Colors looked up and stretched tall
シト
Shito
Rainbow Spring
as the pink spring had swayed
リょーくん
Ryo-kun
Running up the stairs,
向日葵（コーラス：赤飯 ｍａｒｏ．）
Himawari (Chorus: Sekihan       maro.
The park bench we always sat at
のぶなが（コーラス：ｈａｌｙｏｓｙ　ｒｅｃｏｇ）
Nobunaga (Chorus:ｈａｌｙｏｓｙ　ｒｅｃｏｇ）
We'd put our bags down, took deep breaths,
イナカモノ
Inakamono
and played around; Our voices from those days
うさ
（コー
ラス：鎖那
なゆごろう）
Usa
(Chorus: Sana   Nayugorou)
laughed
うさ
Usa
The things we saw, the things we found
みんな
Everyone
paint the sky sunset and return to us
みんな
Everyone
Seeming to look down upon the glittering city,
みんな
Everyone
three drifting clouds swam through the sky
みんな
Everyone
The little birds
have taken flight
シト
Shito
The evening sun
なゆごろう（コー
ラス：赤飯
Nayugorou (Chorus: Sekihan
is sinking far below the horizon
鎖那（コー
ラス：うさ
向日葵）
Sana (Chorus:   Usa  Himawari)
and both the city and sky
イナカモノ
Inakamono
are finally flipped upside down
のぶなが（コー
ラス：
リょーくん）
Nobunaga (Chorus:
Ryo-kun  )
I'd always dreamed as a child
鎖那
Sana
of myself, grown-up and smiling
鎖那
Going up piles of memories,
my crouched-over back
イナカモノ
Inakamono
looked up towards tomorrow
シト
（コー
ーラス：
Shito
(Chorus:
The days we linked arms over shoulders and laughed,
なゆごろう（コーラス：赤飯　リょーくん）
Nayugorou (Chorus: Sekihan  Ryo-kun)
the days we joined hands and rejoiced,
うさ（コーラス：イナカモノ
Usa (Chorus: Inakamono
the days I sadly hung my head,
（コーラス：のぶなが　 向日葵 ）
(Chorus: Nobunaga  Himawari)
the days I spent crying alone in my room
リょーくん（コーラス：鎖那　 なゆごろう  ）
Ryo-kun (Chorus: Sana   Nayugorou)
Write them out page by page,
向日葵
Himawari
and they will change their appearance right here
向日葵
Faces looking up, expressions,
赤飯
Sekihan
warmth, breaths
赤飯
Faint moonlight shines down
なゆごろう（コーラス：
リょーくん）
Nayugorou (Chorus:
Ryo-kun )
and pushes the trees' shadows back to the sky
のぶなが（コーラス：シト　向日葵 ）
Nobunaga (Chorus: Shito  Himawari)
Flower petals swam through the opening,
うさ( コーラス：イナカモノ
Usa (Chorus: Inakamono
closer and closer to the lake
（コーラス：赤飯
(Chorus: Sekihan
and brushed against spring's mirror, causing it to sway
シト〔コーラス：うさ　 向日葵）
Shito (Chorus: Usa  Himawari)
CONGRATULATIONS ON GRADUATION
Congrats!
The classroom door
I left behind
うさ
Usa
continues to close
リょーくん
Ryo-kun
time's bookmark, our memories, even now
赤飯（コーラス：イナカモノ
Sekihan (Chorus: Inakamono
Shadows stretched orange
向日葵（コーラス：
リょーくん）
Himawari (Chorus:
Ryo-kun)
Graduation Ceremony
change my pace
鎖那（コーラス：うさ　シト）
Sana (Chorus: Usa  Shito)
And just like that,
のぶなが
Nobunaga
atop the wind,
turns the pages of the seasons
なゆごろう（コーラス：赤飯
Nayugorou (Chorus: Sekihan
A single feather
鎖那
Sana
takes flight towards tomorrow
The days we ran through
シト（コーラス：うさ　のぶなが ）
Shito (Chorus: Usa  Nobunaga)
connects today, on and on,
向日葵（コーラス：鎖那　シト）
Himawari (Chorus: Sana  Shito)
to hope
のぶなが（コーラス：鎖那　向日葵 ）
Nobunaga (Chorus: Sana  Himawari)
Reflected figures,
リょーくん
Ryo-kun
The sky they looked up at,
and wide-open arms
イナカモノ
Inakamono
turned tomorrow into today
のぶなが（コーラス：
リょーくん）
Nobunaga (Chorus:
Ryo-kun )
and light bloomed
なゆごろう（コーラス：赤飯
Nayugorou (Chorus: Sekihan
The things we saw, the things we found, all of them
みんな
Everyone
surround our hearts and return to us
Our feelings reached far away
and drew a rainbow bridge there
We've begun to walk forwards
Sunlight through the trees filled the world and our beginnings
and radiance marked the time we woke
A gentle breeze aims towards the sky and blows free
Try holding out your hand, see,
it's warm...
Rainbow Spring
Vocals
Inakamono
Usa
Sana
Shito
Sekihan
Nayugorou
Nobunaga
Himawari
Ryo-kun
Illust./Video
Music
FuwariP
Rainbow Spring